{
    "subject": "resource/Paul_Davis_(Kansas_politician)",
    "predicate": "ontology/almaMater",
    "object": "resource/University_of_Kansas",
    "human_readable": "Paul Davis (Kansas politician) attended the University of Kansas.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9846142530441284,
            "question": "Was Paul Davis involved in politics during his time at the University of Kansas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9524658918380737,
            "question": "Did Paul Davis study at a university in Kansas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9046609401702881,
            "question": "Where did Paul Davis attend university?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8992352485656738,
            "question": "What is the name of the university Paul Davis attended?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.80438631772995,
            "question": "What type of institution did Paul Davis attend?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8012627959251404,
            "question": "What state is Paul Davis a politician from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6740509271621704,
            "question": "Is there a connection between Paul Davis's education and his political career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5806257724761963,
            "question": "What field did Paul Davis likely pursue based on his political career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5574662089347839,
            "question": "Is Paul Davis known for his work in politics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39638322591781616,
            "question": "Can you name any other notable alumni from the University of Kansas?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Paul Davis (Kansas politician) attended the University of Kansas.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3754_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Paul Davis known for his work in politics?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3754_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What field did Paul Davis likely pursue based on his political career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3754_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there a connection between Paul Davis's education and his political career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3754_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3754_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3754_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3754_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3754_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3754_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3754_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3754_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3754_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3754_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3754_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format containing the answer:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple, as it is stated that \"Paul Davis is a graduate of the University of Kansas and the Washburn University School of Law.\""
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports Paul Davis's attendance at the University of Kansas. Specifically, both \"8.txt\" and \"31.txt\" mention his graduation from the University of Kansas with a Bachelor of Science in Political Science in 1995."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}